

WENDY

WEB DESIGNER UI/UX DESIGNER



wendyjin2020.github.io/portfolio

PROFILE

I am Wendy, an experienced web and UI/UX designer living in Vaughan. I'm passionate in designing web and mobile applications with neat user interface and clean front-end code.

For each products I've been working on, my goal was always to modernize the aesthetic, empower the user and increase conversions

MAIL ADDRESS

46 Cannes Ave Vaughan ON L4H 4P8 Canada

CONTACT INFO

dbw forever@hotmail.com



416.846.4046

SKILLS

- o Graphic Design
- o Web Design
- o logo & Icon Design
- o UI/UX Design

EXPERIENCE

2020 - now

Freelancing

worked on user interface design for different clients such as Fastapproach.ca and alpremium ca

2016 - 2019

51.ca | Senior Web Designer

Founded in 2001, 51.ca is now the largest online platform of the Chinese community in Canada, providing services in online news, real estate, job listings and more

- Designed user interface for mobile and web APPs
- Planed and executing responsive solutions for existing and new company
- Created responsive landing pages for company events and promotions under tight deadline

2014 - 2015

Wired Messenger | Web Designer

Wired Messenger is a Canadian top email marketing agency based out of Toronto that specializes in email marketing, web design, web development, print and more.

- Coordinated between art director and developers to facilitate the process of building online products
- Created wireframes and HTML prototypes for client's online campaigns and websites
- · Coded HTML emails and ran tests to ensure compatibility in major email providers

2013 - 2014

Tour East Holiday | Graphic and Web Designer

Tour East Holiday is one of the most dynamic and innovative travel companies located in Toronto.

- Planned site structure & created UI for corporation websites
- Coded and integrated Html, CSS and jQuery into DotNetNuke a web content management system and web application framework based on Microsoft NFT
- Created email templates supported by major email platforms and executed email marketing campaigns
- Designed flyers, newspaper ads, brochure for offline marketing promotions

2011 - 2012

Weight Watchers International, Inc. | Web Designer

- Created brand identity for company's blog project and customized WordPress themes
- Conducted research of WordPress widgets to improve blog performance
- Worked with overseas developers to solve technical issues effectively through daily virtual meetings
- Designed newsletters, banners and landing pages

2007 - 2010

YesUp Ecommerce Solutions Inc. | Web and Flash Designer

Founded in 1999, YesUp provides the most effective and comprehensive online advertising services and products.

- · Created visual assets, including graphics, logo and icons for websites
- Delivered html prototypes with emphasis on cross browser compatibility
- Created flash games and banners for on-line Ad campaigns
- Created promotional or educational flash demos or videos for company products and services

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree

Diplomat

York University | Administrative Study | Seneca College | Digital Media Arts 2005 - 2007

2002 - 2004